communicationsjobs.net 2013-05-20

# Jobs | Communication & Media Job Listings - CommunicationsJobs.net

### Privacy Policy

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact us or write to us at Beyond.com, 1060 First Avenue, Suite 100, King of Prussia, PA 19406. 

Please take a minute to read the following policy so you understand how we use the personal information we ask you to submit. As we update and expand our services, this policy may change, so please refer back to it periodically. If you use any of our services, you agree to these terms. 

* * *

### Collection and Use of Information

When you register with this site or one of its affiliated web sites, we ask you for personal information. We use this information to process your requests and to communicate with you about the status of your requests. We may also use your email address to send you newsletters to which you are subscribed during registration, as well as messages about any special offers, promotional announcements and consumer surveys, Beyond services, account updates, services that may be of interest to you, or administrative messages regarding your account. Email list options can be managed under your account user settings. 

By registering on or using our site, you consent to the disclosure of your personal information to our partners and affiliates. Beyond does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with third parties or non-affiliated companies, except as otherwise disclosed in this policy, or under the following circumstances:

We disclose information: 

  * to companies and individuals we employ to perform services on our behalf,
  * if legally required to do so,
  * to protect the rights or property of this site or our affiliated companies, or
  * to protect the personal safety of users or the general public.

Additionally, information may be passed on to a third party in the event of a transfer of ownership of our company. 

In order to serve you better and more efficiently, we may also share anonymous aggregated information (relevant to the job search) about users with our partners and other third parties relevant to the job search.

We collect information from our users at several different points on our website. When you first register with us, we ask for your email address and a password. At this time, we may subscribe you to various email publications. You can unsubscribe from any or all publications at any time. If you are a registered member, click here to access your account and manage your email options. We will delete data on our site that you have provided to us, upon request, through our Contact Us form.

We also offer an Associate program, where associate members direct customers to the network through links on their Web sites. We ask associates for their site name (URL), mailing address, primary contact, pay-to address, technical contact, and other site-related information to determine whether a site will be included in our network. The information collected from our affiliates is used strictly for that program; none of this information is used for general marketing purposes. 

In some cases our software and web site are utilized by our partners in a business alliance via their web community. In these cases, the information collected on our site is available to both companies. 

You should be aware that any personal information (such as email address or resumes), which you voluntarily display or distribute on our network and on the Internet can be collected and used by others, no different than posting this information in a newspaper. This may result in your receiving unsolicited messages from third parties for which Beyond.com is not responsible and has no ability to affect. 

This site uses the ClickTale web analytics service, which is not owned, operated or controlled by Beyond.com. We use the information collected by ClickTale service to improve your user experience. ClickTale may record mouse clicks, mouse movements and scrolling activity, as well as any text you type in this website. ClickTale does not collect personally identifiable information that you do not voluntarily enter into this website. ClickTale does not track your browsing habits across web sites which do not use ClickTale services. For more information, see [Privacy Policy for Information Collected by the ClickTale Web Analytics Service](http://www.clicktale.com/privacy_service.aspx). You may disable this Service at <http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html>.

Back to top

* * *

### Viewing and Updating Your Information on the Network

You always have complete access to the information you have provided to the network. You can make changes to this information to update your account anytime. If you are a registered member, you may click here to manage your information.

Back to top

* * *

### Cookies

In general, we have limited use of cookies. As you browse areas of this site, cookies may be placed on your computer's hard drive. (Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your hard drive.) Cookies allow us to track your account so you don't need to retype the information each time you visit our site. You may refuse cookies in your browser, but doing so may result in certain services and features not functioning properly.

Our advertisers may also serve cookies when users click on the ad banners on this site, or use web beacons to collect information. We do not have access to any personal information gathered by advertisers.

If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from collecting data, currently you may either visit each ad network's web site individually and opt out. Notwithstanding anything else in this policy, we or a data provider we have engaged may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, that we may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>

Back to top

* * *

### Cached Information

There may be instances where information you have submitted to Beyond.com is temporarily cached or stored by another site, such as Google.com, even after such information has been removed from the Beyond.com site. These sites are maintained by third parties not controlled by Beyond.com. Accordingly, Beyond.com expressly disclaims any responsibility for the cached information displayed by these third party web sites. 

Back to top

* * *

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Back to top

* * *

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. You may have arrived at this website by clicking on a link from a Beyond.com affiliate or other affiliate. If so, you should be aware that Beyond.com may share your information with that affiliate and the affiliate may use the information in accordance with its privacy policy instead of ours. 

Back to top

* * *

### Recommend a Friend or Colleague

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend or colleague about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. We will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to visit the site or review the content selected by a user. We then store this information in our databases. The friend may contact us to request that we remove this information at any time. 

Back to top

* * *

### Security and Access

We have implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

When you place an order online at this site, your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol. SSL makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted. This site uses a service company to process its credit card transactions.

Users should not post personal information to any site if they are uncomfortable with the security of the site. If you have any questions, please contact us. 

Back to top

* * *

### Children

This site is not intended for children under 13 years of age and we do not knowingly or specifically collect information about children. This site does not and will not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission. We believe that children should get their parents' consent before giving out personal information. If you are concerned about your child's use of this site, we encourage you to use web-filtering technology to supervise your child's access to the site. For children 14 and up (high-school age), we also encourage you to participate in your child's experience with our site. With a little guidance, this site can prove very useful in finding a part-time or summer job for your child, as well as providing them with excellent career counseling information. 

Back to top

* * *

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If at any point you have questions or concerns about Beyond.com's privacy policy, please feel free to contact us. 

Back to top

* * *

Rev. May 2012

* * *
